## Simran Lakhani

simranlakhani123@gmail.com +91 9769525166 Surat, Gujarat

## **Summary**:

Self-motivated and success-driven assistant business manager with experience of over 4+ years; want to be associated with an organization where I can apply my knowledge and skills to contribute in the growth and development of the company's brand.

# **Experience**:

# **Assistant Business Development Manager in Digital Marketing**

WritesIndia – Surat, Gujarat

06/2022 - Present

- \*Make reports for management and administration
- \*Participating in the sales meeting
- \*Building positive relationship with clients
- \*New client's acquisitions
- \*Managing digital marketing requirements
- \*Upwork Bidding

## **Business Development Associate**

Threadbucket Studio LLP - Surat, Gujarat

12/2020 - 05/2022

- \*Managed and maintained a targeted sales with maintaining CRM on Global Platform and generated more revenue for the company by selling products at a little higher rate than local B2B rates
- \*Marketed and promoted sales over online platforms like YouTube and Facebook
- \*Built and maintained relationships with key contacts at potential clients
- \*Handle Customer relations of the company (B2C)

#### **Export Merchandiser**

A.K. Exports & Imports – Surat, Gujarat

07/2019 - 11/2020

- \*Prepare documents for Export
- \*Client's Invoicing
- \*Understand the needs of a client

### **Customer Relationship Manager**

Neo Growth Pvt. Ltd. – Mumbai, Maharashtra

08/2018 - 03/2019

- \*Understanding key customer individual needs and addressing them
- \*Resolved customer complaints quickly and efficiently
- \*Built and maintained profitable relationships with key customers
- \*Maintained a positive attitude focused on customer satisfaction

### **Skills**:

- \*Good communication and persuasion skills
- \*Energetic and dedicated performance
- \*Able to communicate politely and presentation skills
- \*Adapt to challenging environments
- \*Good interpersonal skills and customer acquisition

### **Technical Skills:**

- \*Microsoft Office Word, Excel and PowerPoint Presentations.
- \*Upwork
- \*Fiverr

# **Education:**

### **Masters in Commerce**

University of Mumbai - Mumbai, Maharashtra

•Currently pursuing Masters in Commerce (Part - 2)

•Masters in Commerce (Part - 1) 2019-2020

o First class with distinction

### •Bachelors in Commerce

Hinduja College of Commerce 2018- 2019

o First class

#### •H.S.C

Hinduja College of Commerce 2015-2016

o First class

### •S.S.C

Diamond Jubilee High School (ICSE board) 2013-2014

o First class with distinction

### **Personal Information:**

Father's Name: Raju Lakhani Sex: Female

Date of Birth: 27th September 1997

Place of Birth: Gujarat

Language Known: English, Hindi and Gujarati

Marital Status: Single

Religion: Ismaili Muslim

Hobbies: Reading, Travelling, Listening to music, Internet Google Search Values &

Strengths: Hard Working, Co-operative & Confident

-Open to relocation

-References can be provided if needed

Place: Surat

**SIMRAN R LAKHANI**